<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<jokes>
    <joke>
        <id>1</id>
        <content>Did you hear about the blind carpenter who picked up his hammer and saw?</content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>2</id>
        <content>Did you hear about the deaf shepherd who gathered his flock and heard (herd)?</content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>3</id>
        <content>
            A teacher is talking to a student.
            Teacher: Did your father help you with your homework?
            Student: No, he did it all by himself.
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>4</id>
        <content>
            A: "I was born in California."
            B: "Which part?"
            A: "All of me."
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>5</id>
        <content>
            A man was complaining to a railroad engineer.
            Man: What's the use of having a train schedule if the trains are always late.
            Engineer: How would we know they were late, if we didn't have a schedule?
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>6</id>
        <content>
            A: "Excuse me. Do you know the way to the zoo?"
            B: "No, I'm sorry I don't."
            A: "Well, it's two blocks this way, then one block to the left."
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>7</id>
        <content>
            Q: What has many keys but can't open any doors?
            A: A piano.
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>8</id>
        <content>
            Q: Can a kangaroo jump higher than the Empire State Building?
            A: Yes, because the Empire State Building can't jump!
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>9</id>
        <content>
            A: Why are you late?
            B: There was a man who lost a hundred dollar bill.
            A: That's nice. Were you helping him look for it?
            B: No, I was standing on it.
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>10</id>
        <content>
            In the classroom the teacher is asking a student to do something.
            Teacher: Tell me a sentence that starts with "I."
            Student: I is the ...
            Teacher: Stop! Never put "is" after "I." Always put 'am' after "I."
            Student: OK. I am the ninth letter of the alphabet.
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>11</id>
        <content>
            A teenage girl had been talking on the phone for about half an hour, and then she hung up.
            "Wow!," said her father, "That was short. You usually talk for two hours. What happened?"
            "Wrong number," replied the girl.
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>12</id>
        <content>
            A: Hey, man! Please call me a taxi.
            B: Yes, sir. You are a taxi.
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>13</id>
        <content>
            A student is talking to his teacher.
            Student: "Would you punish me for something I didn`t do?"
            Teacher:" Of course not."
            Student: "Good, because I haven't done my homework."
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>14</id>
        <content>
            The mother says to her daughter, "Did you enjoy your first at school?"
            The daughter answers, "First day? Do you mean I have to go back again tomorrow?"
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>15</id>
        <content>
            Two boys were arguing when the teacher entered the room.
            The teacher says, "Why are you arguing?"
            One boy answers, "We found a ten dollor bill and decided to give it to whoever tells the biggest lie."
            "You should be ashamed of yourselves," said the teacher, "When I was your age I didn't even know what a lie was."
            The boys gave the ten dollars to the teacher.
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>16</id>
        <content>
            A: Doctor, will I be able to play the piano after the operation.
            B: Yes, of course.
            A: Great. I never could before.
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>17</id>
        <content>
            In the first year of marriage, the man speaks and the woman listens.
            In the second year of marriage, the woman speaks and the man listens.
            In the third year, they both speak and the neighbors listen.
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>18</id>
        <content>Love is one long sweet dream, and marriage is the alarm clock.</content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>19</id>
        <content>
            The teacher says: Today, we're going to talk about the tenses. Now, if I say "I am beautiful," which tense is it?
            The student says: Obviously it's the past tense.
        </content>
    </joke>
    <joke>
        <id>20</id>
        <content>
            Two factory workers are talking.
            The woman says, "I can make the boss give me the day off."
            The man replies, "And how would you do that?"
            The woman says, "Just wait and see." She then hangs upside-down from the ceiling.
            The boss comes in and says, "What are you doing?"
            The woman replies, "I'm a light bulb."
            The boss then says, "You've been working so much that you've gone crazy. I think you need to take the day off."
            The man starts to follow her and the boss says, "Where are you going?"
            The man says, "I'm going home, too. I can't work in the dark."
        </content>
    </joke>
</jokes>